Operations to perform:
  Apply all migrations: accounts, accounts_ledger, admin, auth, contenttypes, customers, inventory, invoices, payments, products, purchases, sales, sessions, vendors
Running pre-migrate handlers for application admin
Running pre-migrate handlers for application auth
Running pre-migrate handlers for application contenttypes
Running pre-migrate handlers for application sessions
Running pre-migrate handlers for application widget_tweaks
Running pre-migrate handlers for application accounts_ledger
Running pre-migrate handlers for application accounts
Running pre-migrate handlers for application core
Running pre-migrate handlers for application customers
Running pre-migrate handlers for application dashboard
Running pre-migrate handlers for application documents
Running pre-migrate handlers for application inventory
Running pre-migrate handlers for application invoices
Running pre-migrate handlers for application payments
Running pre-migrate handlers for application products
Running pre-migrate handlers for application purchases
Running pre-migrate handlers for application reports
Running pre-migrate handlers for application sales
Running pre-migrate handlers for application vendors
Running migrations:
  No migrations to apply.
  Your models in app(s): 'customers', 'invoices', 'payments', 'products', 'purchases', 'vendors' have changes that are not yet reflected in a migration, and so won't be applied.
  Run 'manage.py makemigrations' to make new migrations, and then re-run 'manage.py migrate' to apply them.
Running post-migrate handlers for application admin
Running post-migrate handlers for application auth
Running post-migrate handlers for application contenttypes
Running post-migrate handlers for application sessions
Running post-migrate handlers for application widget_tweaks
Running post-migrate handlers for application accounts_ledger
Running post-migrate handlers for application accounts
Running post-migrate handlers for application core
Running post-migrate handlers for application customers
Running post-migrate handlers for application dashboard
Running post-migrate handlers for application documents
Running post-migrate handlers for application inventory
Running post-migrate handlers for application invoices
Running post-migrate handlers for application payments
Running post-migrate handlers for application products
Running post-migrate handlers for application purchases
Running post-migrate handlers for application reports
Running post-migrate handlers for application sales
Running post-migrate handlers for application vendors
